
const STORE = [
    {
      question: 'Which state is NOT visible from the top of the Sears Tower?',
      answers: [
        'Illinois',
        'Ohio',
        'Michigan',
        'Indiana'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'Ohio'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which artist is NOT from Chicago?',
      answers: [
        'Kanye West',
        'Kaskade',
        'Fall Out Boy',
        'Eminem'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Eminem'
    },
    {
      question: 'What do Chicagoans call the Cloud Gate?',
      answers: [
        'The Bean',
        'Windy Gate',
        'Second City',
        'Chicago Cloud'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'The Bean'
    },
    {
      question: 'Chicago River is the only river in the world that...',
      answers: [
        '...has goldfish.',
        '...is undrinkable.',
        '...flows backward.',
        '...freezes during the winter.'
        ],
      correctAnswer: '...flows backward.'
    },
    {
      question: 'How is Chicago\'s hot dog unique from other cities?',
      answers: [
        'No mustard',
        'No ketchup',
        'No pickles',
        'No sesame seeds'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'No ketchup'
    },
    {
      question: 'The Chicago Cubs won the World Series in 2016 after how many years?',
      answers: [
        '52 years',
        '2 years',
        '88 years',
        '108 years'
        ],
      correctAnswer: '108 years'
    },
    {
      question: 'What rumor do most people believe caused the Chicago Fire of 1871?',
      answers: [
        'Mrs. O’Leary’s cow kicked over a lamp and set her barn on fire',
        'Daniel ‘Pegleg’ Sullivan set Mrs. O’Leary’s barn on fire while trying to steal milk',
        'A meteor shower',
        'Mr. Cohn knocked over a lantern while illegally gambling in Mrs. O’Leary’s barn'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'Mrs. O’Leary’s cow kicked over a lamp and set her barn on fire'
    },
    {
      question: 'How many of the top 20 tallest buildings in the USA are in Chicago?',
      answers: [
        '5',
        '6',
        '7',
        '8'
        ],
      correctAnswer: '6'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which Chicago improvisational comedy enterprise did Tina Fey, Steve Carell, Stephen Colbert, and Bill Murray come from?',
      answers: [
        'Up Comedy',
        'iO Theater',
        'The Second City',
        'Chicago Improv'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'The Second City'
    },
    {
      question: 'How many rings did Michael Jordan win with the Chicago Bulls?',
      answers: [
        '10',
        '7',
        '8',
        '6'
        ],
      correctAnswer: '6'
    }
];
